{
    "subject": "Agrippina_the_Younger",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Claudius",
    "human_readable": "Agrippina the Younger is married to Claudius.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9722129106521606,
            "question": "Was Agrippina the Younger in a relationship with Claudius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9576919674873352,
            "question": "Is Agrippina the Younger related to Claudius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9369195699691772,
            "question": "Who was Agrippina the Younger married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9063192009925842,
            "question": "What is Claudius's connection to Agrippina the Younger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8810212016105652,
            "question": "To whom was Agrippina the Younger wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8363375067710876,
            "question": "Who was Claudius married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8199760317802429,
            "question": "Agrippina the Younger's husband is a significant figure in Roman history. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7956525087356567,
            "question": "Who was the partner of Agrippina the Younger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7913772463798523,
            "question": "What is the name of Agrippina the Younger's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7504721879959106,
            "question": "Agrippina the Younger's spouse is known as...?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Agrippina the Younger is married to Claudius.",
            "html": "yago_26738_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Agrippina the Younger's husband?",
            "html": "yago_26738_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the partner of Agrippina the Younger?",
            "html": "yago_26738_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Agrippina the Younger's husband is a significant figure in Roman history. True or False?",
            "html": "yago_26738_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26738_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can evaluate the query \"Agrippina the Younger is married to Claudius\".\n\nHere's the result:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents suggest that Agrippina was indeed married to Claudius, with multiple mentions of their marriage in different files."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that support the statement \"Agrippina the Younger is married to Claudius.\" For instance, one document states, \"Agrippina\u2019s marriage to Emperor Claudius, her second husband, was a master class in scheming behind the scenes,\" and another mentions, \"Agrippina marries her uncle Claudius\" along with specific details of their marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}